So, now you have some experienced building and using a linear regression model.
所以 现在你有一些经验丰富的建筑和使用线性回归模型
In your last project,
在你的最后一个项目中
the data was prepared for you.
数据是给你准备的
However, there's often a lot of work that goes into gathering,
但是 很多很多的工作都在收集
cleaning, and blending data before it's ready for analysis.
清洁 并在数据准备好进行分析之前对数据进行混合
Data preparation is absolutely crucial for business analysis.
数据准备对于业务分析绝对至关重要
Without good data prep,
没有好的数据
the results of your analysis can be incorrect or misleading.
您的分析结果可能不正确或具有误导性
For example, while I was working as a consultant,
比如我在做顾问的时候
I was building a model to estimate the price of
我正在建造一个模型来估算
a stock based on movements in marketing industry indices.
以营销行业指数的走势为基础的股票
It was pretty late in the process when my colleague pointed out that the stock price was
我的同事指出股票价格是很晚的
listed it as negative on some days which totally threw everything off.
在一些日子里把它列为负面 完全把一切都抛在了身上
After making the changes,
在做出改变之后
the results of my analysis made much more sense.
我的分析结果更有意义
In this next section,
在下一节
we will discuss various aspects of preparing
我们将讨论准备工作的各个方面
data including how to avoid mistakes like Sam's.
包括如何避免山姆的错误
You learned about different data sources and data types,
您了解到不同的数据源和数据类型
how to deal with common data issues like missing data and outliers,
如何处理常见的数据问题 例如缺少数据和离群值
how to format data,
如何格式化数据
and how to blend data from different sources.
以及如何融合来自不同来源的数据
Take a look at the project overview and description before you go through the course.
请先查看项目概述和描述 然后再通过课程
It will give you a good sense of the goal of the course. Good luck.
它会让你对课程的目标有好感  祝你好运。
最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6